晚上好  巧克力帅哥
Evening, hot chocolate.
麦克斯  小中国惹大麻烦了
Max, we got big trouble from little China.
你好  麦克斯
Hi, Max.
"大"麻烦吗
Big trouble?
瞧他那"小"样
There's nothing big about him.
就跟夹娃娃机的娃娃差不多大
He looks like I won him in a bear claw machine.
麦克斯  你最不想从阿憨的嘴里
Max, what is the worst sentence you ever want to hear
听到哪句话
come out of Han's mouth?
我把你肚子搞大了
I got you pregnant?
拜托  更惨绝人寰一点
Come on, bad, bad.
我把你的肚子又搞大了一次
I got you pregnant again?
是"我要装卡拉0K"
I'm putting in karaoke.
不  不行
No! No!
憨
Han...
那些家伙之所以在上面
Those guys better be up there
最好是因为我们要把"股沟"加进餐单
because we're officially putting ass crack on the menu.
我装电视是为了要吸引顾客
I am adding a TV to bring in more customers.
我们可以举办主题之夜  如终极格斗之夜
We can have theme nights, Ultimate Fighting nights,
正宗绝望主妇之夜
Real Desperate Housewives of Bravo City nights,
最棒的是
and best of all,
卡拉OK之夜
karaoke night.
给嬉皮士麦克风可是大忌
You can't get hipsters on microphone.
那是在火上浇油  助纣为虐
That's like throwing gasoline on a pretentious fire.
嬉皮士喜欢卡拉OK呢
Hipsters like karaoke.
句子换成  嬉皮士"希特勒"卡拉OK
Replace the word "like" with the word "Hitler"
史上最烂的三样人事物就大团圆了
and you got the three worst things in history.
麦克斯  我懂你的意思  但是
Max, I hear what you say, but
* 大家一起来欢呼 *
* Everybody else say "he-ey!" *
* 单身女性站起来 *
* Where are my single ladies! *
好  下一位将演唱凯蒂·佩里的《少女梦》
Okay. Next person is going to sing Teenage Dream by Katy Perry,
大美女凯蒂以前可是痤疮大丑女呢
who is pretty now but used to have very horrible acne.
短短的45分钟里  我都听了三遍《少女梦》了
This is the third Teenage Dream in 45 minutes.
我用收银机夹暴自己蛋蛋都没这么难受呢
Why don't I just close my nuts in the cashier's drawer?
上场吧  史黛丝小姐
Come on up now, girl named "Stacey."
这事儿交给我吧
I got this.
虽然我不认识你  但我对你有好感
Look, I don't know you, but I like you.
我也很尊重你发型的"二"样化
And I respect both hair choices.
我恨死卡拉OK了
I hate karaoke.
我脑袋里  憎恨已经满档
I can't afford to have any more hate in my head.
恨意一触即发
My hate is at capacity.
你不献唱  我就送你个水果派
Sit this one out, I'll comp your cobbler.
你这是干嘛
What did you do?
拯救厄尔快疼爆的蛋蛋
I saved Earl's nuts.
上菜  美味出炉  快上菜
Pick up! Hot food. Pick up.
别对我猛按铃  奥列格
Calm your bells down, Oleg.
不是我服务的区
Not my stations.
卡洛琳呢
Where's Caroline?
如果我说她刚和我在后边
Would it make you jealous if I said
"激情"了一番  你会吃醋吗
she was back here with me?
吃醋倒不会
Jealous? No.
生气是肯定的
Pissed? Probably.
店里超忙  我还要花时间解开
Because we're busy and it would take me all that time
你用来捆绑她以逞兽欲的胶布
to get the duct tape off her mouth and hands.
你在里面干嘛呢  白雪公主
What are you doin' in here, snow white?
如果想找你的小矮人
If you're lookin' for one of your dwarves,
其中一只在外面拿着麦克风呢
he's out there, holding the mic.
瞧  我的咬合错位了
Look, my bite is off.
这是我做的咬合检查
See, I did the bite test.
第七号牙和第九号牙重叠了
The number seven incisor is crossing over number nine.
慢着  你还知道自己牙齿的编号名吗
Hold up. You know the names of your teeth?
你不知道吗
Don't you?
我连我亲爹的名字都不知道
I don't even know the name of my father.
哎哟  我刚咬到舌头了
Ow, I just bit my tongue.
第十二号也来瞎搅和了
Ah! Number 12 just joined the party.
快停止你这举动
I'd stop doing that right now.
你这一幕被存进奥列格的意淫银行了
You just made it into Oleg's spank bank.
恭喜你哟
Congratulations.
牙齿保持器没了  我还怎么活啊
What am I gonna do without my bite guard?
我的牙会到处乱跑的
My teeth don't know where to go.
就让它们去旅行个几年  找到人生方向
Well, maybe they should just backpack for a couple of years,
就不会乱跑了
so they figure it out.
听好了  美牙妹
Listen, perfect teeth,
这是我人生中的恶梦
this is a nightmare for me.
用专业术语来说就是"中重度磨牙症"
The technical term for this is "advanced bruxism."
专业术语来说  你有"过度小题大做症"
And the technical term for you is "overly dramatic."
昨天家里没厕纸你就哭天喊地
Yesterday you freaked out 'cause we were out of toilet paper.
憋到上班的时候再上就好啦  大家都这样
Just hold it till you get to work like everybody else.
趁大家在等餐  我来献唱一曲吧
Now, maybe I sing while others wait.
完蛋  这才是真正的麻烦
Uh-oh. We got real problems now.
我从苏珊大妈的网络剪辑中
I choose Susan Boyle popular song
选出了一首她的成名曲
from all clips on Internet.
名叫《我曾有梦》
It's called I Dream--
做你的白日梦吧
Keep dreaming.
你回来啦
Oh, you're back.
我们还以为你逃家了呢
We thought you ran away.
我和栗宝都准备要去收容所
Chestnut and I were just about to pick out
再捡个人回来养了
another human from the shelter.
今天倒霉死了
I had quite a day.
八点至十点  磨  磨  疼
8:00 to 10:00... Grind, grind, pain.
十点至十一点  疼  疼  磨
10:00 to 11:00... Pain, pain, grind.
所以我去药店
So I went to the drug store
买了个八块钱的牙齿保持器
and bought an $8 bite guard,
结果不合我恐怖片般的牙型
which didn't fit my freaky Tim Burton mouth.
后来我去退货的时候
And when I tried to return it,
那个收银员  朗达
the cashier, Rhonda,
虽然胸牌上写着"乐于服务顾客"
whose nametag said she was happy to help,
结果却凶巴巴的  还百般刁难我
but who was neither happy nor helpful,
她说不能退货
said that I couldn't return it
因为这玩意儿已经接触过我的牙"翅"了
because it had already touched my "teef."
作为一个下巴快掉的人
For someone whose jaw is about to unhinge,
你怎么还不少说点话
you're sure flapping it a lot.
为什么这有份写我老爸的小报
Why is this rag with my father on it here?
瞪我干嘛  是栗宝买的
Don't look at me. Chestnut bought it.
他喜欢我给他念每日星"马"座
He likes it when I read him his daily horse-oscope.
为什么大家都要对他的闭口不谈
Why is everybody so obsessed with the fact that
穷追猛打呢
he hasn't said anything?
你没有过卡壳并无言以对的时候吗
Haven't you ever been at a loss for words?
卡棉条有过  卡壳倒不会
Tampons, yes. Words, nah.
来做件让自己好受些的事
Well, this will make me feel better.
每当我痛苦时  我就得享受一下
Whenever I'm in pain, I need a treat.
每当你痛苦时  我都超级享受
You know, whenever you're in pain, that is my treat.
寿司  希望你会喜欢蟹卷
Sushi! I hope you like crab roll.
我从来没吃过寿司
I never had sushi.
这根本是是胡扯中的鬼扯
That doesn't even make sense.
没吃过寿司  没看过牙  什么人啊这是
No sushi, no dentist... Who are you?
穷人
A poor person.
寿司没点技术含量
Sushi's lazy.
要是我去日本餐厅
If I come to your restaurant,
一定吼他们去把鱼给我煮熟了
get up off your ass and cook the damn fish.
真希望我们能有钱去
I wish we could afford to go to this little sushi place
我爸以前常带我去的日本小餐馆
in Tribeca where my father always took me.
每次我们进店里
We had this little joke.
都会开同一个玩笑  我总会说
Every time we'd walk in, I'd always say...
然后我们就捧腹大笑
And we would just laugh!
所以你说日语也还是冷场女皇
So you're not funny in Japanese either.
我在转角的熟食店买的
I got this at a corner deli.
那个收银员是个日本人
The cashier was Japanese.
她说这个很好吃
She said it was good.
肯定是真的啊
Oh, I'm sure it's great.
因为无公民权利的移民人士
'Cause the disenfranchised immigrant
服务被宠坏的白人女孩时
serving the spoiled white girl
肯定不会骗她
would have no reason to lie.
享受美味到上天堂的感觉吧
Get ready for something heavenly!
难吃到下地狱
That's not heaven.
快吐出来
Spit it out.
真是太不济了
What a disappointment.
你的第一次就这么毁了
Your first time.
我的"第一次"都是这种下场
Well, that's kinda the way it goes with me and first times.
给  把身上擦擦干净
Here, clean yourself off.
简直是历史重演  一模一样
That's exactly the way it goes!
没那么糟
It's not that bad.
没那么糟  真没那么糟
It's not that bad. It's not that bad.
没错
No.
地铁站里的牙科诊所
For a dentist office in the subway,
这家算是"不错"了
it's pretty good.
说真的  你怎么还不夺门而逃啊
Seriously, how are you not running out of here?
我别无选择
I have no choice.
我现在既没钱也没医疗保险
Now that I have no money or health insurance,
我不得不适应第三世界的环境
I have to get used to this third-world situation.
这哪里是第三世界
Third-world situation?
这根本就是冥界
This is an underworld situation.
好吧  这里有防弹玻璃
Okay, there's bulletproof glass.
上面还有颗子弹
With a bullet in it.
好啦  至少说明这玻璃管用
All right, so the glass works.
这儿说要登记
It says to sign in.
你干嘛不直接拿开店基金
Look, why don't you just take some of our cupcake business savings
去看好点的牙科诊所呢
and go to a good dentist office?
就是那种不会因为看一眼地板
You know, one where you won't get a staph infection
就染上传染病的诊所
just from looking at the floor.
不  不能这么做
No, we can't do that.
那笔钱可是我们的未来
That's our future.
花了一次
Once we start doing that,
之后就难以回头了
it's a slippery slope.
"妮可·瑞奇"
"Nicole Richie"?
我不想让人知道我来过
I don't want anyone to know I was here.
我知道这里的环境不够理想
I know this situation is less than ideal,
但我现在有紧急"牙"况
but I am having a dental emergency.
不  他才有紧急"牙"况
No, he's having a dental emergency.
走吧  去那边问问
Come on, let's go over here
看他能不能帮帮我
and see if this man can help me.
你好
Hi.
欢迎来到地铁开口笑
Welcome to Subway Smiles.
不是说了马上就到你吗
I told ya, we'll get to ya.
抱歉  女士们
I'm sorry, girls.
我现在有点发抖
I'm a little shaky.
我刚被枪击了
I was just shot at.
我的牙齿有移位的问题
I have a problem with my teeth migrating.
我有中重度磨牙症
I have advanced bruxism.
我有丙型肝炎
Ah. I have hep C.
人生在世  谁无小病
Everybody's got their something.
你需要什么
What do you need?
我们需要离开
We need to be leaving.
我需要个牙齿保持器
I just need a bite guard.
这个我会
Oh! I can do that.
我得先喷点白沫进你嘴里
That's where I squirt foam into your mouth
做个牙模
and make a mold.
到后面来吧
Come in the back.
要跟他进后面
If you go back there with him,
不光需要牙齿保持器  还需要防强暴器
you'll need a bite guard and a rape guard.
你要用笑气吗
You want the gas?
有必要吗
Is that necessary?
不用你会后悔的  小甜心
You're gonna want the gas, sweetheart.
在打烊前  再来一首
One more song before we close.
就来首辣妹合唱团的
I sing Spice Girls'
* 告诉我你想要什么 *
* Aww, tell me what you want, *
* 你内心深处最强烈的欲望 *
* what you really, really want. *
他歌喉僵硬的程度
That boy's more stiff
比米歇尔·巴赫曼的老公看男妓时还"硬"呢
than Michele Bachmann's husband at a Chippendales.
我给你钱  让你去看好牙医吧
I will give you the money for trip to fancy dentist.
真的吗  奥列格  你愿意吗
Really? Oleg, you would do that?
就当是我帮你个忙
It's favor I do for you.
日后我需要你帮忙时
And at some point, when I come to you for favor,
你也会果断答应  就像我现在这样
you will say yes, like I say yes now.
我得知道你会要我帮什么忙
Well, I'd need to know what that favor might be.
这还说不定
I can't say for sure.
是一周内还是一个月内
Will it be in a week or a month?
这个我也不确定
I can't say for sure.
跟性有关系吗
Will it be sexual?
是的  有关
Yes, it will be.
这我确定一定以及肯定
This I can say for sure.
多谢  还是算了吧
Thank you, but no.
我真是个白痴
I am such an idiot.
这开头好  接着说
I like it. Keep going.
我的保持器就在我家别墅的厕所里
My bite guard is just sitting in the bathroom of my townhouse.
如果我能爬上屋顶
If I could only get up on the roof,
我就可以从天窗溜进去
then I could break in through the skylight
就像高中时溜出来那样
like I used to when I snuck out in high school.
你好  我是麦克斯  你还是大小姐吗
Hello, I'm Max. Have we met?
我十五岁的时候  贿赂了装安保系统的人
When I was 15, I paid the security system guys extra
让他们不要在天窗装感应器
to not wire the skylight,
之后我偷溜出去参加朋友的十六岁派对
and then I snuck out and went to Ilana Shapiro's Sweet 16...
-不错  -跑到希腊呢
- Cute. - In Greece.